Contact

tejureddi8893@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tejaswinireddy-gundumalla-5b67b2150 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Business Intelligence (BI)

Tableau

SQL

Certifications

Tableau Designer
Tableau Desktop Specialist
Tableau Analyst
Tableau Consumer
Tableau Author

Tejaswini Reddy Gundumalla

Business Intelligence Developer

Hyderabad

Summary

BI Professional with 5+ years of experience working in Financial and Pharmaceutical Industries who has a broad range of skills dealing with data extraction to report generation. Experienced working in Agile Methodology on BI tools like Tableau, Microsoft SQL Server, Infomatica, SSIS and TIBCO Spotfire.

Experience

Synchrony Senior Analyst June 2018 - Present (2 years 3 months) Hyderabad, Telangana

Infosys

Senior System Engineer December 2014 - June 2018 (3 years 7 months)

Hyderabad Area, India

Education

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University, Hyderabad Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Electrical and Electronics Engineering · (2010 - 2014)